# **JACKSON PLATT**

PORTLAND, OR | (971) 226-0573 JACKSON.B.PLATT@GMAIL.COM

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a strategic storyteller who is attending Oregon State University. My curiosity has guided me to take internships in politics, marketing, data, and videography. My technical skillset ranges from having extensive professional practice in Adobe Creative Suite to having published research in social network data analytics.

# **SKILLS**

- Advertising and marketing
- Storytelling

- Data analytics
- Video production

# **EDUCATION**

# **EXPECTED IN MARCH 2021**

**Bachelor of Arts:** New Media Communications | GPA: 3.91

Oregon State University, Corvallis, OR

Member and Huntsman Cancer Institute Chairman of the Beta Pi Chapter of Sigma Chi Fraternity

# **WORK HISTORY**

## **OCTOBER 2018-CURRENT**

**Oregon State University Alumni Foundation** | Video Production Intern My job is to tell the collective narrative of the Oregon State University community. By using fine-tuned storytelling, we build a stronger relationship between our alumni and our school. I work in every step of the process, from strategy to production.

Please check out our published content: <a href="https://vimeo.com/osufoundation">https://vimeo.com/osufoundation</a>

## **NOVEMBER 2019-CURRENT**

**Communications, Editorial, and Marketing Director** | TEDxOregonState TED Talks is a global initiative designed to spread ideas. As the Marketing Director, my job is to lead a dedicated team to create and manage a strong online presence of our event. This includes managing and creating website content, our blog, and a strong social media presence.

#### **NOVEMBER 2019-CURRENT**

**Legislative Intern** | Oregon State House Of Representaives

Major aspects of my position include Identifying, researching and tracking legislative issues relevant to current public issues. I have gained professional experience in gathering research and presenting conclusions.

## RESEARCH

Through a collaboration with the OSU College of Public Health, I researched social network frames regarding the Carona Virus Outbreak. Using a Twitter API our group established social frames regarding public perception of the outbreak.

https://medium.com/@danfaltesek/do-not-cover-this-easy-story-corona-virus-conspiracy-theories-are-almost-all-robots-552ad23342e5